landlordology.com 2013-12-24

# Privacy Policy // Landlordology

**Privacy Policy for  **landlordology.com

**_Your privacy is critically important to us. At Landlordology we have a few fundamental principles:_**

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact us.

Landlordology LLC. (“ **Landlordology** ”) operates Landlordology.com. It is Landlordology’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

### **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Landlordology collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Landlordology’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Landlordology’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Landlordology may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Landlordology also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on our website.

### **Notice Concerning Children**

PLEASE NOTE: We are a general audience site, and do not direct any of our content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a Site user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

### **Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**

Certain visitors to Landlordology’s website choose to interact with Landlordology in ways that require Landlordology to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Landlordology gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at Landordology.com to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Landlordology are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Landlordology collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Landlordology. Landlordology does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Landlordology discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Landlordology’s behalf or to provide services available at Landlordology’s website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Landlordology’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Landlordology will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Landlordology discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Landlordology believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Landlordology, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of a Landlordology website and have supplied your email address, Landlordology may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Landlordology and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Landlordology takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### **Automatic Collection**

Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

### **Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Landlordology uses cookies to help Landlordology identify and track visitors, their usage of Landlordology website, and their website access preferences. Landlordology visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Landlordology’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Landlordology’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### **Business Transfers**

If Landlordology, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Landlordology goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Landlordology may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### **Ads**

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Landlordology and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### **Third Party Websites**

The website contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we have no control over the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

### **Public Comments**

The Site may include interactive sections such as commenting areas where visitors to the site can post comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### **Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel contact us at the following:

Lucas”at”landlordology.com

### **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Landlordology may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Landlordology’s sole discretion. Landlordology encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this website after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### **Change log:**

  * _September 27, 2012:_  Initial Release
